重写onCreate()方法  并使用我们在合约类中定义的常量
Modify onCreate to create
the LocationEntry database table using
来创建LocationEntry数据库表
the constants we defined
in the contract.
好消息是这个声明和WeatherEntry很相似
The good news is that
this is a similar but
但是又更简单
simpler statement than what
we have in WeatherEntry.
你将会创建并执行一个存储了SQL命令的字符串
You'll be creating and executing
a string that stores an SQL command.
你需要确保每一个列使用了正确的数据类型
You want to make sure to use
the correct data types for each column.
你同样需要确保使用了正确的约束
Also, make sure that you
have the right constraints.
通常  对于Weather表的所有模型
In general, for
all the model of the weather table.
除了ID列  其它列必须定义成不能为空
With the exception of the ID,
all columns must be defined as not null.
地点查询应该额外加上唯一性
The location query should
additionally be defined as unique or
经纬度为实数或者浮点数
coordinates are real, or
floating point values.
你应该考虑为SQL声明语句加上输出日志
You should consider adding logging
statements to print the SQL statement,
以便验证语句是自己期望的样子
and verify that it
looks as you intended.
特别注意空格、插入语以及逗号
Pay close attention to spaces,
parenthesis, and commas.
写好了创建表的SQL语句以后
Once you have finished writing
the SQL to create the table,
继续去运行TestDB中的testCreateDB()测试方法
continue to run testCreateDB
from within the TestDB, and
让这个测试引导你进行创建表的声明语句的调试
let it guide you as to how to
fix your creation statement.
当你结束了编码以后  我建议你看一下我们的解决方案
Once you have finished coding,
I recommend looking at our solution,
以防我们测试漏了什么
just in case our test missed something.